gailonline.com 2006-05-27

# GAIL's Privacy Policy

T _his website_ ( **http://www.gailonline.com** ) _is provided as a public information service of the GAIL (India) Limited._

If you visit this site to read or download information, it must be known that GAIL collects and stores a standard set of Internet-related information, such as an Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time, the type of browser and operating system used, the page(s) visited. All information is collected to help the company makes this site more useful to our customers and is only used for statistical purposes.

If you choose to provide us with personal information such as through our "User Feedback" or in an e-mail to GAIL or to an employee of the company, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information for any purpose other than to respond to you.

### SECURITY

Unauthorised attempts to defeat or circumvent security features, to use the system for other than intended purposes, to deny service to authorised users, to access, obtain, alter, damage, or destroy information, or otherwise to interfere with the system or its operation is prohibited. Evidence of such acts may be disclosed to law enforcement authorities and result in criminal prosecution under the applicable laws.

For site security purposes, and to ensure this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy or the confidentiality provisions for information submitted on the website of GAIL, please contact [webmaster@gail.co.in](mailto:%20webmaster@gail.co.in)
